Yes gas welcome back you are in the video so
brother whoever asked where is your TVS Rudder,
brother my TVS Rudder is gone,
after the claim brother the
claim people have troubled me a lot and till now nothing has
changed in it, firstly this has not changed,
look look this has not changed here,
what all has not changed and its
rear pot, this back panel has not changed, so there
was a scratch on it
today, it is from the side, they had put it
in the claim, so till now it has
not been done and the second thing, what do you
say about ours, this mirror, they had put it in,
I took it from someone else's bike, put
something of my own, changed it and by making jugaad I have bought
such an expensive bike, 125 cc
cycle and first of all I don't know whether it was a
third class service center, when you bought it from it,
after that you took the story, I don't have this
method,
where will the
process go, tell me on which date did you give the bike, I
bought this one on 9th January, I
bought it on 9th January and when should
we go to the service center to take the claim  When did you go on
8th I am fine and when did you get the car you
got the car on 8th at least 12th or 13th it is
even after 12th or 13th that means one month and
4-5 days are gone just the panel now mother what if
if there was some fault in the engine then for how many days they would have taken it
mother what do you say this car is
for us whom will you buy the car we will keep it if it is
of some other bike
what is the matter
then again there is
just a scratch fault in me so there is no such thing
like when it goes on high speed the light comes on
automatically okay so this is one issue
and secondly what is the second one the
top speed which you were telling is now
₹16 after doing it sometimes
its gears go up and down gears go up and
down means it is not the same as before first of all
I will tell you what all changes have happened in it
brother first of all these lights have been completely changed so the
insurance benefit is there that much is fine I
mean the bike is from a good company so it is from a very
good company  If you go to a good dealership, it is
much better, they changed the mudguard and
gave it to me. This panel of
ours, the right panel was damaged, there were
scratches on it, yes the mechanic did one thing, I do
n't know
what it was called, so
in the process of this, I do
n't know how it is done,
what actually happens to it, it is gum oil, it is called dot three
oil, it doesn't even apply it to the body,
look, look, it gives coaching on the upper cat, actually
I will have to apply dubbing only on this, it will get
fixed to some extent with rubbing, I mean it will become like new
and there was some other panel here, this
panel was
very bad, I swear, whatever we told
him, he changed it, it is okay,
but he did not ask whether there is
any problem or something in it while driving,
my silencer was half stuck inside,
he said that it will have to be bent, the
advisor there told the TV,
brother, I will pull it out with a rod,
if it breaks then it is your responsibility,
brother, here, I mean  The silencer
was crooked, it was crooked, look there are scratches here, it was just the
bolt that was going in, it was
not going in the volt, right, now I checked the
iron rod
[Music]
that is also a thing, okay this plate has been changed,
maybe one second these have not been changed
brother, this has not been changed
but what is this, it has gone in one or two places,
I am asking where did the scratches
come from, by the way it is going on, you must have applied paint,
it has come from the side but I do
n't know how this happened, it has happened while keeping it,
but one second brother,
this plate is painted, this is the same old
plate, you have painted and
this old plate has been put in, okay and
look at this part, it has not changed at all, if you
ask to change the silencer, then
how many years does it take,
okay, check the engine oil inside the bike,
lipstick is given to check the engine oil, that's it,
brother, the basic thing is
how much did they charge for this bike
under insurance, that is, the file charge,
₹19000 something was made and out of which they
gave me 1500  It was okay,
how many rounds have we made, we have threatened to go to consumer court,
brother please
clarify, do
you have any complaint with this vehicle, the
product is good to drive,
but they have played games with me, it is
very bad, I swear, for this,
TVS should take action against them, I
mean, I
called them just two days ago, I said to them,
Sir, what should I say, my
rider of 40-45 years has not come forward, Sir, he has
not come yet, how will it go, we will inform you, it is going to be
12 months, yes, maybe it is the 2nd, it is a
₹33000 vehicle,
this month, till now the S16
people have given, next time you will get third
party insurance, like I have
5 years insurance, first party for one year
and everything else is third party, next time get it done from
a good company, first
party
and secondly, we just went to TVS and the
service experience there is
bad, no, no, they would have
opened the engines of scooters, brother, I am surprised by this thing,
start it for a minute, brother, it will be
fine on the stand, right?  Now friends, just see this, the
entire car is running, look at this, look at this, look at this, in fact, so much clutch, so many clutches,
he has left the clutch completely empty and there is so much
hard gearing going on
inside it,
look
brother, I don't understand what the person setting the clutch was doing,
what had he done, I can't understand anything,
but brother, he did not set the car on red,
next time brother, we will go to another service center,
how many free service backups are there right now, it has
two backups, it has two backups,
from which angle it is free, it costs Rs. 12:30, I do
n't know from which angle it is free,
it is decreasing with you too, for
my Rs. 1250 fridge
oil it costs Rs. 400, I don't know
what is written in it, I
spent Rs. 700, 12:30, that's all, I am thinking of
going and talking to him under a completely new name, I
said, you have free service from home,
what is the free service of by free service, I
mean, this scan that is going on, let's settle it,
whatever it is,
friend, we will get it serviced from outside  The
oil costs ₹500, ₹200 or ₹300, service
charge five plus eight plus ₹700 or ₹800,
if you look into it the company
recommends 10w30, you can also buy synthetic,
Castrol power one up
to 5.580, you will get a good genuine one
which will also have engine flash, now if you remove that also, then
in mutual
you will get very good oil of max to max 5.5 or 600 for
10-30 and
after putting that, the performance and what
happens, there will be another filter inside it, is it a
paper filter or the like, that is,
it is form type, it is
not confirmed, so see what happens many times
and the filter goes
inside it after getting cleaned, mother, this filter of ₹100 is done, the
oil is done, if the bill comes then how much will be
your
service bill till now, how much did the
500 one cost for 500 km  And the
second thing will happen now, this time, whatever
trick I will tell you, do the same,
ask them that brother, what are you putting in it,
we don't need it in a new car,
brother, is there any need for engine flashing, if the
engine has to be flashed then
why do we have to change the oil after 500 kms, brother, because
after 500 kms,
because this is what happens, brother, after 500 kms, the
oil company asks to change it,
as if it is made by the company, now you also see
that CNC line, if any part moves,
it will wear out, the parts inside it will wear out,
so what happens in the car which is coming packed from the company, is that if the
part is
worn out, then it is worn out, that is why the company which gives engine oil first, gets
it removed after 500 kms
so that along with it, the
slightly worn out sawdust gets
removed, okay, if you are doing this in the first 500 kms, that is the
rule, then
why are you putting Indian flash, then why are you putting oil treatment, do
send me that service page once, I would like to see it
and next time  No, you should go, it will only
cost you the fuel, you don't have to pay any money for the free service
brother, first of all this
was the entire experience brother, after 250 km the
car has run 25000 rupees and
inside it brother, no doubt there is no problem inside the car, there is no issue
with the mileage also, so the
car is very good but getting the TVS
service done from a place which is
quite popular in your area, then this will end
and if you are going to buy a TVS rudder or
you do not have any claim on the insurance, is this
your bike or any other brother, then keep this thing in mind
that you should take insurance from a good company, till then
Jai Hind Vande Mataram
subscribe button is here
brother